Shen Tianbai.
Hello.
You don't remember me?
Who are you?
I'm Lu Ye.
Do you remember who you are?
I...
I am...
A wolf.
Your name is Shen Tianbai.
You're the youngest sheriff in Ningcheng.
You are also the savior in their hearts.
You are not a wolf. You are human.
Have you really forgotten everything?
Get away!
Please,
please remember!
Please!
I remember.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 23]
You finally remember.
It was you
who turned me into this.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I really regret meeting you.
I won't...
I won't give up on you.
Never.
I hate you.
I'm going to kill you.
Calm down.
Thank you for helping me
with another experiment.
The wolf transformation is simply perfect.
I think
you should have figured it out, right?
I promise you.
Good.
Pleasure working with you.
Waiting for you at Tianjiu Alley.
Go!
Don't move!
Young Master,
don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
We are at the end of our rope now.
No.
There is still hope.
Shen Tianbai will bring back
the antidote for the new wolf toxin.
Hasn't Shen Tianbai already
transformed into a wolf?
Has he regained his sanity?
I read in the dean's paper that
wolves have the instinct to hunt
and to protect their pack.
They discovered a phenomenon
in the experiment,
called the imprinting effect.
After a creature completely
transforms into a wolf,
the first person it bites
is called the first blood source,
who is very likely
to be marked as one of them,
awakening the sanity
of the wolf-transformed.
Besides that,
familiar smells,
touch,
and taste
will also help.
I don't know if it will work.
I can only take a gamble.
The moment I saw him,
I knew
I won the bet.
There is an antidote.
I will find it.
So you agreed to the director
just to help him stall for time.
But even if he gets the antidote,
how is he going to pass the message out?
The director has once again tightened
hospital security and added guards today.
Even if he can fight 10 men single‑handed,
well,
once he's discovered,
I'm afraid it'll be too late.
Don't worry.
Shen Tianbai always keeps his word.
He definitely won't break his promise.
We misjudged him before.
This man would rather die to trick us
into keeping the experiment going.
For a fanatical, paranoid,
and arrogant scientist like him,
the only person he trusts
is himself.
The origin is the end.
[Renji Hospital]
Shen Tianbai!
Did you kill the chief?
Whether it was me or not,
you should already know.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have followed the director.
I want to avenge the chief,
but I don't know what to do.
I'm so useless.
There is someone who can help you.
Who?
Lu Ye.
Lu Ye?
The antidote for wolf toxin is actually...
So,
only he can save Ningcheng.
What if he doesn't believe me?
After all, I...
I stabbed him.
He will believe you.
Because he knows I won't break my promise.
Okay.
Tell me what to do.
Help me take something out.
The director doesn't trust me now.
I...
Don't worry.
You can do it.
Tell me
what you want me to take.
Young Master Lu,
do your job well.
If you do well,
the director will reward you heavily.
But if you don't,
you know better than me
what will happen to the Qingtian Gang.
Yes.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Murder!
Shen Tianbai killed someone!
Help!
Murder!
Shen Tianbai killed someone!
Shen Tianbai went berserk
while having his blood drawn!
Didn't I tell you
not to draw that much at once?
A bunch of idiots!
What are you waiting for?
Give him a tranquilizer!
Yes!
Watch out, Director!
Calm down.
I didn't actually want to kill you.
Don't do this.
What's going on?
It seems to be the hospital.
Shen Tianbai,
I said you were the savior,
and you actually believed it.
As expected,
only you
could come up with such a method.
I'll leave it to you,
Lu Ye.
You won.
Leave the rest
to me.
I will
definitely win too.